Guide to the Publisher's Archive: Hommes pour Hommes, circa 1989-2003.
Publisher's Archive: Hommes pour Hommes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Publisher's Archive: Hommes pour Hommes, circa 1989-2003.
7816
Koskovich, Gerard.
1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The business records, submissions of erotic-narrative letters, and submissions of and responses to personal ads for Hommes pour Hommes, a gay sexual-contact magazine produced in Paris, covering the period 1990 until it ceased publication in 2003.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Real desires/fantasies and the end of an era in the world of print, Hommes pour Hommes was a magazine that catered to gay men who were looking for sexual partners. It started in 1990, and in 1996 was renamed Le Nouveau HH: Le magazine gay des rencontres. The magazine went out of business in 2003, apparently due to the move of this activity to the Internet, which happened in France several years later than in the United States.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The business records, submissions of erotic-narrative letters, and submissions of and responses to personal ads for Hommes pour Hommes, a gay sexual-contact magazine produced in Paris, covering the period 1990 until it ceased publication in 2003. In addition, a file of materials from a swinger's magazine from the same publisher and a number of the personal-ad letters from couples seeking a third sexual partner for bisexual activities. The collection provides a window into French gay men's desires and fantasies in the 1990s, as well as into the final years of the era of print media as the setting for arranging sexual contacts.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Koskovich, Gerard.
Subjects:
Gay personals.
Places:
France -- Social life and customs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
For 75 years from the date of any correspondence, personal narratives and other writing, researchers may not reveal the names of the private individuals who wrote or were mentioned therein. All users of the collection will sign an agreement to abide by this restriction.
CONTAINER LIST
- Administrative records and miscellaneous, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Lettres announces, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Lettres reponses, 1989-1990's (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Lettres reponses, 1989-1990's (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lettres reponses, 1989-1990's (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Personal ads, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Personal ads, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- File of material from a swinger's magazine, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Poster advertising posting of announcements and contacts via Hommes pour Hommes using Minitel (a precursor of the World Wide Web), n.d.; O/S Folder 1